picocent.com 2013-06-03

# Privacy Policy - Picocent - Contribute with less than a cent

_Picocent, Inc._  

_Privacy Policy  _  
This privacy policy was last modified on October 13, 2012. 

Picocent, Inc. ("Picocent," "we," or "us") knows that you care how information about you is used and shared. This Privacy Policy explains what information of yours will be collected by Picocent when you use Picocent.com and related services (the "Service"), how the information will be used, and how you can control the collection, correction and/or deletion of information. We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy. 

If you have questions about the Privacy Policy or would like to suggest improvements, please contact us at info@picocent.com. 

_Information We Collect  _  
User-Provided Information: You provide us information about yourself, such as your name and e-mail address, when you register with the Service. If you correspond with us by email, we may retain the content of your email messages, your email address and our responses. 

Cookies Information: When you visit Picocent.com, we may send one or more cookies - a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters - to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser and lets Picocent help you log in faster and enhance your navigation through the site. A cookie does not collect personal information about you. Picocent uses both session cookies and persistent cookies. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser's directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of the Service may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled. 

Log File Information: Log file information is automatically reported by your browser each time you access a web page. When you register with or view our site, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends whenever you visit any website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, referring / exit pages and URLs, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed, and other such information. 

Clear Gifs Information: When you use the Service, we may employ clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons) which are used to track the online usage patterns of our users anonymously. No personally identifiable information from your Picocent account is collected using these clear gifs. In addition, we may also use clear gifs in HTML-based emails sent to our users to track which emails are opened by recipients. The information is used to enable more accurate reporting, improve the effectiveness of our marketing, and make Picocent better for our users. 

_How We Use Your Information  _  
We use the personal information you submit to operate, maintain, and provide to you the features and functionality of the Service. 

Any personal information or content that you voluntarily disclose for posting to the Service (for instance, in Projects or other User Content you post) becomes available to the public. If you remove User Content, copies may remain viewable in cached and archived pages or if other users have copied or stored your User Content. 

By providing Picocent your email address you consent to our using the email address to send you Service-related notices, including any notices required by law, in lieu of communication by postal mail. You may not opt out of some Service-related communications. However, you can change the frequency of many Service-related communications by changing the settings in the "Settings" section. We may also use your email address to send you other messages, including changes to features of the Service and special offers. If you do not want to receive such email messages, you may opt out by changing the settings in the "Settings" section. 

Opting out may prevent you from receiving email messages regarding updates, improvements, or offers. 

Picocent may use certain information about you and/or your User Content without identifying you as an individual to third parties. We do this for purposes such as analyzing how the Service is used, diagnosing service or technical problems, maintaining security, and personalizing advertisements and promotions. 

Picocent reserves the right, but has no obligation, to monitor the User Content you post on the site. Picocent has the right to remove any such information or material for any reason or no reason, including without limitation, if in its sole opinion, such information or material violates, or may violate, any applicable law or our Terms of Service agreement or to protect or defend its rights or property or those of any third party. Picocent also reserves the right to remove information upon the request of any third party. 

We use cookies, clear gifs, and log file information to: (a) remember information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the site; (b) provide custom, personalized content and information; (c) monitor the effectiveness of our service; (d) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors and traffic; (e) diagnose or fix technology problems reported by our users or engineers that are associated with the IP addresses controlled by a specific web company or ISP; and (f) help you efficiently access your information after you sign in. 

_How We Share Your Information  _  
Personally Identifiable Information: Picocent will not rent or sell your personally identifiable information to others. Picocent may share your personally identifiable information with third parties solely for the purpose of providing services to you. If we do this, such third parties' use of your information will be bound by this Privacy Policy. We may store personal information in locations outside the direct control of Picocent (for instance, on servers or databases co-located with hosting providers). 

As we develop our business, we may buy or sell assets or business offerings. Customer, email, and visitor information is generally one of the transferred business assets in these types of transactions. We may also transfer such information in the course of corporate divestitures, mergers, or dissolution. In any such transfer of information, your user information would remain subject to this Privacy Policy. 

Except as otherwise described in this privacy statement, Picocent will not disclose personal information to any third party unless required to do so by law or subpoena or if we believe that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the law, comply with legal process served on us or our affiliates, or investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual illegal activities; (b) to enforce our Terms of Service, take precautions against liability, to investigate and defend ourselves against any third-party claims or allegations, to assist government enforcement agencies, or to protect the security or integrity of our site; and (c) to exercise or protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Picocent, our users or others. 

Non-Personally Identifiable Information: We may share non-personally identifiable information (such as anonymous usage data, referring/exit pages and URLs, platform types, number of clicks, etc.) with interested third parties to help them understand the usage patterns for certain Picocent services. 

Picocent allows other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements on the Picocent site. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on Picocent. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content. 

Picocent does not provide any personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent. However, please note that if an advertiser asks Picocent to show an advertisement to a certain audience and you respond to that advertisement, the advertiser or ad-server may conclude that you fit the description of the audience they are trying to reach. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers or ad networks. The Picocent privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such advertisers. 

_How We Protect Your Information  _  
Picocent uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Picocent and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission of information, Picocent makes commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards. 

To protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps (such as requesting a unique password) to verify your identity before granting you access to your account. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your unique password and account information, and for controlling access to your email communications from Picocent, at all times. 

_Compromise of Personal Information  _  
In the event that personal information is compromised as a result of a breach of security, Picocent will promptly notify those persons whose personal information has been compromised, in accordance with the notification procedures set forth in this Privacy Policy, or as otherwise required by applicable law. 

_Your Choices About Your Information  _  
You may, of course, decline to submit personally identifiable information through Picocent, in which case Picocent may not be able to provide certain services to you. You may update or correct your account information and email preferences at any time in the "Settings" section. 

_Children's Privacy  _  
Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, Picocent does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register. If you are under 13, please do not send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under age 13 is allowed to provide any personal information to or on Picocent. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at info@picocent.com. 

_Links to Other Web Sites  _  
We are not responsible for the practices employed by Web sites linked to or from our Web site nor the information or content contained therein. Please remember that when you use a link to go from our Web site to another Web site, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other Web site, including those that have a link on our Web site, is subject to that Web site's own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding. 

_Notification Procedures  _  
It is our policy to provide notifications, whether such notifications are required by law or are for marketing or other business related purposes, to you via email notice, written or hard copy notice, or through conspicuous posting of such notice on our Website page, as determined by Picocent in its sole discretion. We reserve the right to determine the form and means of providing notifications you, provided that you may opt out of certain means of notification as described in this Privacy Policy. 

_Changes to Our Privacy Policy  _  
If we change our privacy policies and procedures, we will post those changes on our website to keep you aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we may disclose it. You are bound by changes to the Privacy Policy when you use the site after those changes have been posted.
